The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series VII: Silverman Administrative Files, 1974-2010
  - Subseries VII.E: Accessions
    In accordance with Museum policy, access is restricted to this entire subseries until 2038. Accessions files, which document Collection purchases, were arranged in three ways: by accession number; alphabetically grouped by seller name; and individually by seller name. Information about the same purchases may appear in more than one set of files. In addition to documenting acquisitions (including provenance and purchase information), these files often contain substantial notes, correspondence, and research about the materials acquired (artworks, publications, or archival documentation), including correspondence with the artists whose work is being purchased. Also sometimes included are "accession sheets" produced by the Silverman Collection, photocopies or photographs of works acquired, contact sheets, and auction catalogues. Files sometimes included the acquisitions themselves, which were moved during processing (to other series, to the Museum collection, or to the Library). In addition to these files, information about acquisitions may found in throughout the Collection, especially in subseries VII.A: General Administrative Files.
    - Subseries VII.E.1: Accessions by Accession Number
      These files were compiled and organized primarily by Jon Hendricks. This organization by accession number (96.15 denoting the 15th acquisition in 1996) has been retained. These numbers may be found on objects in the Archive as well as artworks and books in the Museum collection and Library. For more information about Silverman Collection numbering systems, see note in front matter.
      Folder titles contain the individual or organization from which the materials were acquired. Files concern the acquisition of the materials listed in the folder description. Numbers 92.19, 00.19, 02.01, 02.02, and 03.10 were either skipped or are missing. In one instance, two separate accessions were assigned the same number (06.01). The archivist assigned bracketed accession numbers to unnumbered files found here, based on their place within the run. When accessions information was known, but no documentation was present, the archivist inserted empty folders into the run.
      - Accessions 1989-1995, Includes summaries of accessions by accession number. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.1)
      - 87.01 - Leokadija Maciunas and Nijole Valaitis, 1987; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.2)
      - 89.01 - Dick Higgins, 1989; Dick Higgins audio tape library, with works by Eric Andersen, Nam June Paik, and Richard Maxfield. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.3)
      - 89.02 - Leokadija Maciunas, 1989; Correspondence from, photographs of, and works by Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.4)
      - 89.03 - Alison Knowles, 1989; Materials, mostly correspondence, by or concerning George Brecht, Robert Filliou, Nam June Paik, Dick Higgins, Emmett Williams, Jackson Mac Low, Takao Saito, and Alice Hutchins. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.5)
      - 89.04 - Yoko Ono, 1989; Works by Yoko Ono. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.6)
      - 89.05 - Shirley Smith, 1989; Work by George Maciunas and photocopies of materials related to the Fluxhouse Co-ops. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.7)
      - 89.06 - Jaroslaw Kozlowski, 1989; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.8)
      - 89.07 - Leokadija Maciunas, 1989; Regards acquisition of correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.9)
      - 89.08 - Michou Strauch-Barelli, 1989; "Fluxus in Nice" contact prints (includes performances by Ben Vautier, George Brecht, and Robert Filliou). (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.10)
      - 89.09 - Leokadija Maciunas, 1989; Family photographs of Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.11)
      - 89.10 - Dick Higgins, 1989; EMPTY (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.12)
      - 89.11 - Marcel Alocco, 1989; Works by Marcel Alocco. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.13)
      - 89.12 - Jeff Berner, 1989; 1 of 2 folders. Work by Jeff Berner and related correspondence to Jeff Berner from Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.14)
      - 89.12 - Jeff Berner, 1989; 2 of 2 folders. Work by Jeff Berner and related correspondence to Jeff Berner from Maciunas. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.15)
      - 89.13 - Jeff Perkins, 1989; Works by Yasunao Tone and Tony Cox. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.16)
      - 89.14 - Bici Forbes, 1989; Works by Jone Jones, Maciunas, and Bici Forbes. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.17)
      - 90.01 - Michou Strauch-Barelli, 1990; Photographs and contact sheets of Fluxus events. (Box 329, Folder VII.E.1.18)
      - 90.02 - Jonas Mekas, 1990; 1 of 2 folders. Includes design works by Maciunas for Fluxus editions by Mieko Shiomi, Ken Friedman, Albert Fine, Ben Vautier, Shigeko Kubota, Robert Filliou, Fluxus Collective, Robert Watts, Claes Oldenburg, George Brecht, Maciunas, Milan Knžk, and James Riddle. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.19)
      - 90.02 - Jonas Mekas, 1990; 2 of 2 folders. Works and other materials by Maciunas. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.20)
      - 90.03 - Emily Harvey Gallery, 1990; Work by George Brecht. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.21)
      - 90.04 - Billie Maciunas, 1990; Publications. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.22)
      - 90.05 - Harry Ruh, 1990; Work by Paul Sharits. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.23)
      - 90.06 - Monika Kinley, 1990; Files of Victor Musgrave, including documentation concerning Fluxshoe. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.24)
      - 90.07 - Jean Noel Herlin, 1990; Publication. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.25)
      - 90.08 - Emily Harvey Gallery, 1990; Works by Nam June Paik. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.26)
      - 90.09 - Harry Ruh, 1990; Publications; issues of Suck and Hit Week; ephemera; photographs. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.27)
      - 90.10 - Dick Higgins, 1990; Work and archival documentation by Dick Higgins. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.28)
      - 90.11 - Jean Noel Herlin, 1990; Publications. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.29)
      - 90.12 - Mildred S. Lee, 1990; Work by Joe Jones. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.30)
      - 90.13 - Harry Ruh, 1990; Issues of Kunst Van Nu. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.31)
      - 90.14 - Reinhold Brown Gallery, 1990; 1 of 4 folders. Work by and correspondence to Albert Fine. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.32)
      - 90.14 - Reinhold Brown Gallery, 1990; 2 of 4 folders. Work and correspondence by George Brecht and Larry Poons (mailed to Albert Fine). (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.33)
      - 90.14 - Reinhold Brown Gallery, 1990; 3 of 4 folders. Correspondence to Albert Fine by George Brecht, Robert Watts, and Ray Johnson. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.34)
      - 90.14 - Reinhold Brown Gallery, 1990; 4 of 4 folders. Works by, and correspondence to, Albert Fine, from George Brecht, Robert Watts, and Ray Johnson, Willem de Ridder, Maciunas, David Mayor, John Cage, (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.35)
      - 90.15 - Betty Asher, 1990; Fluxus I. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.36)
      - 91.01 - La Monte Young and Marian Zazeela, 1991; Works by Maciunas and Fluxus collective. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.37)
      - 91.02 - Reinhold Brown Gallery, 1991; Work by George Brecht. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.38)
      - 91.03 - Sotheby's, 1991; Work by Maciunas, Yoko Ono, and John Lennon. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.39)
      - 91.04 - Michou Strauch-Barelli, 1991; Work by Ben Vautier. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.40)
      - 91.05 - Harry Ruh, 1991; Works by Willem de Ridder, Wolf Vostell, and Wim T. Schippers. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.41)
      - 91.06 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 1 of 2 folders. Works by Fluxus Collective, Maciunas, Claes Oldenburg, Joe Jones, George Brecht, Nam June Paik, and Ben Vautier. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.42)
      - 91.06 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 2 of 2 folders. Works by Takako Saito, Ay-O, and Toshi Ichiyanagi; works and working materials by Maciunas. (Box 330, Folder VII.E.1.43)
      - 91.07 - Billie Maciunas, 1991; Work by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.44)
      - 91.08 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 1 of 4 folders. Box of negatives assembled by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.45)
      - 91.08 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 2 of 4 folders. Box of negatives assembled by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.46)
      - 91.08 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 3 of 4 folders. Box of negatives assembled by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.47)
      - 91.08 - Jonas Mekas, 1991; 4 of 4 folders. Box of negatives assembled by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.48)
      - 91.09 - Billie Maciunas, 1991; [Unknown] (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.49)
      - 91.10 - Barbara Moore, 1991; Work by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.50)
      - 91.11 - Turtle Island Booksellers, 1991; An Anthology. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.51)
      - 91.12 - Knud Pedersen, 1991; Photographs from Fluxus festival in Copenhagen. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.52)
      - 92.01 - Philip Corner, 1992; Works by Yoriaki Matsudaira and Shuko Mizuno; ephemera. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.53)
      - 92.02 - Yoko Ono, 1992; Work by Yoko Ono. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.54)
      - 92.03 - Galerie 1900-2000, 1992; Work by George Brecht. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.55)
      - 92.04 - Tomas Schmit, 1992; Correspondence to Tomas Schmit from Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.56)
      - 92.05 - Harry Ruh, 1992; Works by and archival materials concerning Willem de Ridder. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.57)
      - 92.06 - Dick Higgins, 1992; Film by Dick Higgins. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.58)
      - 92.07 - Harry Ruh, 1992; Work by Willem de Ridder. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.59)
      - 92.08 - Hollis Melton, 1992; Work by Maciunas and Billie Hutchins. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.60)
      - 92.10 - Jon Hendricks, 1992; Work by Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.61)
      - 93.01 - Jonas Mekas, 1993; 1 of 2 folders. Works by Maciunas, Milan Knžk, Fluxus Collective, George Brecht; correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.62)
      - 93.01 - Jonas Mekas, 1993; 2 of 2 folders. Works by Maciunas, Milan Knžk, Fluxus Collective, George Brecht; correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.63)
      - 93.02 - Jonas Mekas, 1993; Video by Jonas Mekas. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.64)
      - 93.03 - Jeff Berner, 1993; Work by Jeff Berner for Fluxus festival in San Francisco. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.65)
      - 93.04 - Harry Ruh, 1993; Work by Milan Knžk. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.66)
      - 93.05 - Harry Ruh, 1993; Photograph of Misha Mengelberg. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.67)
      - 93.06 - Harry Ruh, 1993; Work by Paul Sharits. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.68)
      - 93.07 - Alison Knowles, 1993; Negatives of photographs by Alison Knowles of Fluxus events. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.69)
      - 93.08 - Harry Ruh, 1993; Works by Robin Crozier, Dick Higgins, and Albert Fine; archival documents concerning Willem de Ridder, Dick Higgins, George Brecht and Robert Filliou. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.70)
      - 93.09 - Kunsthaus Lempertz, 1993; 1 of 3 folders.Fluxkit. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.71)
      - 93.09 - Kunsthaus Lempertz, 1993; 2 of 3 folders.Fluxkit and work by Joe Jones. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.72)
      - 93.09 - Kunsthaus Lempertz, 1993; 3 of 3 folders. This folder contains auction catalogue. (Box 331, Folder VII.E.1.73)
      - 93.10 - Roy Slade, 1993; 1 color slide of Robert Filliou performance. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.74)
      - 94.01 - Kunsthaus Lempertz, 1994; Works by Benjamin Patterson, La Monte Young, Cornelius Cardew, and Dieter Roth. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.75)
      - 94.02 - Harry Ruh, 1994; Publications; cassette tapes. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.76)
      - 94.03 - Manfred Leve, 1994; Photographs by Manfred Leve. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.77)
      - 94.04 - Mieko Shiomi, 1994; Works by Mieko Shiomi. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.78)
      - 94.05 - Mieko Shiomi, 1994; Works by Mieko Shiomi, La Monte Young, Ay-O, and Fluxus Collective. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.79)
      - 94.06 - Dorine Van Der Klei, 1994; Photographs and ephemera from Fluxus performances. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.80)
      - 94.07 - Hermann Braun, 1994; Regards trade to Hermann Braun of work by George Brecht for work by Takako Saito and George Brecht. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.81)
      - 94.08 - Antiquariat M. + R. Fricke, 1994; Work by Maciunas and Nam June Paik; ephemera. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.82)
      - 94.09 - Jeff Perkins, 1994; Video of Fluxfilm by Jeff Perkins. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.83)
      - 94.10 - Dick Higgins, 1994; Manuscript by Dick Higgins. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.84)
      - 94.11 - Mieko Shiomi, 1994; Works by Mieko Shiomi. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.85)
      - 94.12 - Teruo Nishiyama, 1994; Photographic documentation of Flux Week in Tokyo and other events. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.86)
      - 94.13 - Jon Hendricks, 1994; Archival material concerning Maciunas. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.87)
      - 94.14 - Steven Leiber, 1994; EMPTY (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.88)
      - 94.15 - Lure Art Books, 1994; Archival material concerning Wolf Vostell and Willem de Ridder. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.89)
      - 94.16 - Jonas Mekas, 1994; Fluxus poster. (Box 332, Folder VII.E.1.90)
      - 94.17 - Bruce Fleming, 1994; Photographs and negatives from "Festival of Misfits." (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.91)
      - 94.18 - Jonas Mekas, 1994; Materials by or concerning Maciunas. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.92)
      - 94.19 - Hermann Braun, 1994; Materials by or concerning George Brecht and Maciunas. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.93)
      - 94.20 - Roy Slade, 1994; Color slides of Robert Filliou performance. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.94)
      - 94.21 - Michou Strauch-Barelli, 1994; Photographs of Ben Vautier and other Fluxus performances. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.95)
      - 94.22 - UBU Gallery, 1994; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.96)
      - 94.23 - Jonas Mekas, 1994; 1 of 2 folders. "Fluxus-Inventory of Jonas Mekas by Tobias Berger." (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.97)
      - 94.23 - Jonas Mekas, 1994; 2 of 2 folders. Works by Larry Miller, Albert Fine, Maciunas, Ben Vautier, Yoko Ono, Nam June Paik, Yoshimasa Wada, Fluxus Collective, Geoffrey Hendricks, Paul Sharits, Mieko Shiomi, and Eric Andersen. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.98)
      - 94.24 - Michou Strauch-Barelli, 1994; Photographs by Marcel Alocco. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.99)
      - 94.25 - Gilbert Silverman, 1994; Works by Arman. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.100)
      - 95.01 - Harry Ruh, 1995; Works by Stanley Brouwn. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.101)
      - 95.02 - Gallery 360, 1995; Work by Nam June Paik. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.102)
      - 95.03 - Hermann Braun, 1995; Works by George Brecht. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.103)
      - 95.04 - [Unknown], 1995; Work by Joseph Beuys and Nam June Paik. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.104)
      - 95.05 - Harry Ruh, 1995; Work by Dick Higgins, Ken Friedman, Robert Watts, Willem de Ridder. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.105)
      - 95.06 - Hans Sohm, 1995; Regards trade to Hans Sohm of elements from Fluxus Yearbox II for work by Robert Watts. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.106)
      - 95.07 - Harry Ruh, 1995; Works by Maciunas, La Monte Young; materials from Happening & Fluxus exhibition. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.107)
      - 95.08 - Galerie 1900-2000 (Marcel Fleiss), 1995; Works by Geoffrey Hendricks, Ben Patterson, Robert Watts, George Brecht, Jock Reynolds, James Riddle, Maciunas, Ken Friedman, Shigeko Kubota, Yoshimasa Wada, Takako Saito, Willem de Ridder, John Chick, Milan Knžk. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.108)
      - 95.09 - La Monte Young and Marian Zazeela, 1995; Ephemera. (Box 333, Folder VII.E.1.109)
      - 95.10 - Jan Van Der Marck, 1995; Works by George Brecht, Arman, Gnther Uecker, Allan Kaprow, and James Lee Byars. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.110)
      - 96.01 - Nantenshi Gallery, 1996; Regards trade to Nantenshi Gallery of work by Ay-O for work by Emmett Williams. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.111)
      - 96.02 - Alison Knowles, 1996; Work by Alison Knowles. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.112)
      - 96.03 - Robert Watts Studio Archive, 1996; Work by Robert Watts. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.113)
      - 96.04 - Hermann Braun, 1996; Regards trade to Hermann Braun of work by George Brecht, Robert Watts, and Alison Knowles for work by Joe Jones. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.114)
      - 96.05 - Am Here Books, 1996; Work by George Brecht. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.115)
      - 96.06 - Finn Falkersby, 1996; Works by Arthur Køpcke, Eric Andersen, and Emmett Williams. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.116)
      - 96.07 - UBU Gallery, 1996; Works by Maciunas and Mieko Shiomi. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.117)
      - 96.08- UBU Gallery, 1996; Works by Maciunas and Henry Flynt. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.118)
      - 96.09 - Rafael Vostell Gallery, 1996; Work by Nam June Paik. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.119)
      - 96.10 - UBU Gallery, 1996; Works by Maciunas. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.120)
      - 96.11 - UBU Gallery, 1996; Works by Maciunas, Larry Miller, and Barbara Moore. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.121)
      - 96.12 - Leokadia Maciunas / Nijole Valaitis, 1996; Personal journals of Leokadia Maciunas. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.122)
      - 96.13 - Galerie 1900-2000 (Marcel Fleiss), 1996; Works by George Brecht. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.123)
      - 96.14 - Track 16 Gallery, 1996; Works by Ben Vautier, La Monte Young, and Nam June Paik. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.124)
      - 96.15 - Hermann Braun, 1996; Regards trade to Hermann Braun for work by George Brecht and Nam June Paik. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.125)
      - 96.16 - Armin Hundertmark, 1996; Work by Takako Saito. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.126)
      - 96.17 - Ben Vautier, 1996; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.127)
      - 96.18 - Finn Falkersby, 1996; 1 of 4 folders. Includes works by Arthur Køpcke, Fluxus Collective, Emmett Williams, and Dick Higgins. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.128)
      - 96.18 - Finn Falkersby, 1996; 2 of 4 folders. Works by Arthur Køpcke. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.129)
      - 96.18 - Finn Falkersby, 1996; 3 of 4 folders. Works by Arthur Køpcke. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.130)
      - 96.18 - Finn Falkersby, 1996; 4 of 4 folders. Arthur Køpcke. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.131)
      - [96.19] - Photo Reporters Inc., 1996; Photographs of "Fluxus Internationale Festpiele Neuester Musik." (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.132)
      - [96.20] - Jonas Mekas, 1996; Work by Takehisa Kosugi. (Box 334, Folder VII.E.1.133)
      - 97.01 - John Hunov, 1997; Works by George Brecht and Maciunas. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.134)
      - 97.02 - Barbara Wien, 1997; Works by Emmett Williams. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.135)
      - 97.03 - Barbara Moore, 1997; Works by Ay-O. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.136)
      - 97.04 - Yoko Ono, 1997; 1 of 3: Works by Robert Watts, Fluxus Collective, Takako Saito, Mieko Shiomi, Maciunas, Hi Red Center, Geoffrey Hendricks, and George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.137)
      - 97.04 - Yoko Ono, 1997; 2 of 3: Works by Robert Watts, Fluxus Collective, Takako Saito, Mieko Shiomi, Maciunas, Hi Red Center, Geoffrey Hendricks, and George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.138)
      - 97.04 - Yoko Ono, 1997; 3 of 3: Works by Robert Watts, Fluxus Collective, Takako Saito, Mieko Shiomi, Maciunas, Hi Red Center, Geoffrey Hendricks, and George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.139)
      - 97.05 - Nijole Valaitis, 1997; Works by Maciunas. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.140)
      - 97.06 - Yoko Ono, 1997; Works by Allan Kaprow, Geoffrey Hendricks, Jock Reynolds, Per Kirkeby, Ken Friedman, Yoshimasa Wada, Jack Coke's Farmer's Co-op, Milan Knžk, George Brecht, Jeff Berner, Carla Liss, Robert Watts, Alice Hutchins, John Chick, Benjamin Patterson, Maciunas, Bici Hendricks, and Dan Calendar. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.141)
      - 97.07 - Hermann Braun, 1997; Works by Maciunas and George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.142)
      - 97.08 - Andr Swertz, 1997; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.143)
      - 97.09 - Gallery 360, 1997; Publications. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.144)
      - 97.10 - Hermann Braun, 1997; Works by George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.145)
      - 97.11 - UBU Gallery, 1997; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.146)
      - 97.12 - John Hunov, 1997; Works by Joe Jones, Tomas Schmit, Fluxus Collective, Robert Filliou, Hi Red Center, Mieko Shiomi. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.147)
      - 97.13 - Jean Noel Herlin, 1997; Works by Yoko Ono. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.148)
      - 97.14 - Andr Swertz, 1997; Works by Ben Vautier and Fluxus Collective. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.149)
      - 98.01 - Barbara Moore, 1998; Photograph by Peter Moore. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.150)
      - 98.02 - Dick Higgins, 1998; Works by Dick Higgins. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.151)
      - 98.03 - Jonas Mekas, 1998; Works by Fluxus Collective. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.152)
      - 98.04 - Adrianna Fish, 1998; Works by Yoko Ono. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.153)
      - 98.05 - Hermann Braun, 1998; Works by Robert Filliou and Nam June Paik. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.154)
      - 98.06 - Hermann Braun, 1998; Works by Robert Watts and George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.155)
      - 98.07 - Alison Knowles, 1998; Works by George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.156)
      - 99.01 - Barbara Wien, 1999; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.157)
      - 99.02 - Hermann Braun, 1999; Works and archival material by George Brecht. (Box 335, Folder VII.E.1.158)
      - 99.03 - Jonathan Geldzahler, 1999; Work by La Monte Young and Marian Zazeela. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.159)
      - 99.04 - Philip Corner, 1999; Works by Philip Corner. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.160)
      - 99.05 - Emmett Williams, 1999; Works by Emmett Williams. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.161)
      - 99.06 - Harry Ruh, 1999; Works by Harry Ruh. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.162)
      - 99.07 - Christie's, 1999; Work by Geoffrey Hendricks. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.163)
      - 00.01 - Hermann Braun, 2000; Works and archival material by Dick Higgins. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.164)
      - 00.02 - Emmett Williams, 2000; Works by Emmett Williams. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.165)
      - 00.03 - Bound and Unbound (Charlotte Moorman), 2000; Work by Karlheinz Stockhausen. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.166)
      - 00.04 - Henning Christiansen, 2000; Publications by Henning Christiansen, Eric Andersen, and Maciunas. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.167)
      - 00.05 - Heart Fine Art, 2000; Works by Milan Knžk. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.168)
      - 00.06 - Jon Hendricks, 2000; Notes concerning Claes Oldenburg. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.169)
      - 00.07 - Emmett Williams, 2000; Works by Emmett Williams and Robert Filliou. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.170)
      - 00.08 - Milan Knžk, 2000; Works by Milan Knžk. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.171)
      - 00.09 - Kevin Concannon, 2000; Works by Toshiro Mayuzumi. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.172)
      - 00.10 - Armin Hundertmark, 2000; Works by Tomas Schmit and La Monte Young. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.173)
      - 00.11 - Bound and Unbound (Charlotte Moorman), 2000; Works by La Monte Young. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.174)
      - 00.12 - Jeff Perkins, 2000; Works by Yoko Ono. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.175)
      - 00.13 - Hermann Braun, 2000; Works by Robert Watts (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.176)
      - 00.14 - Barbara Wien, 2000; Works by Ben Vautier. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.177)
      - 00.15 - Gilbert Silverman, 2000; Work by Maciunas. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.178)
      - 00.16 - Galerie 1900-2000, Work by Ay-O. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.179)
      - 00.17 - Barbara Wien, 2000; Works by Arthur Køpcke. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.180)
      - 00.18 - George Brecht, 2000; George Brecht notebooks. (Box 336, Folder VII.E.1.181)
      - 00.20 - John Hunov, 2000; 1 of 6 folders. Works by Stanley Brouwn, Fluxus Collective, news clippings and ephemera from "Festum Fluxorum/Musik OG Anti-Musik Det Instrumentale Teater." (Box 337, Folder VII.E.1.182)